Portfolio

thecraigharvev.co.uk

Front End Skills

HTML5 CSS 3 SASS Bootstrap AngularJS Angular Vue JS

Back End Skills

PHP
MySQL
Node JS
Express
MongoDB
HTTP
RESTful API
ASP.NET / C#

Software Skills

GIT
Webpack
Command Line
Postman
Slack
Photoshop
Illustrator
Sketch App

Soft Skills

Responsive Design Mock up Creation Prototype Creation

About

I am a graduate of the City of Glasgow College with an HND in Web Development. I have a background in architecture and have always had a passion for new technology and the web. I enjoy making bespoke interactive web experiences and love learning new technologies and techniques.

Education

Aug 2016 - June 2018
City of Glasgow College
HND Web Development

Sept 2003 - May 2009 **Robert Gordon University**MArch Architecture

BSC (Hons) Architecture 2:1

Work Experience

Mar 2015 – Aug 2016 **Working Holiday** New Zealand

July 2010 - Feb 2015
Architectural Officer

Aberdeen City Council. Aberdeen Responsible for delivering a full architectural service on a wide range of project including environmental upgrades and accessibility works.

Aug 2009 – July 2010 **Plumbers Assistant**BMH Plumbing and Heating. Aberdeen

June 2008 - Sept 2008 Joiner's Assistant

Kenny Gaitor Joinery. Aberdeen

Jul 2006 - Jul 2007

Architectural Assistant

Saunders Architects. Welwyn Garden City University placement working a on a range of feasibility studies and speculative developments.